[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Can I sing later?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "sing", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "You can sing later.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "sing", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Mr. Showbiz?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Showbiz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Showbiz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "How are you, daddy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "daddy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Are you getting much sleep?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "getting", "much", "sleep", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, you know, I never sleep.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "never", "sleep", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Are you a good nappy changer?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "nappy", "changer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "ORGAN: Diapers?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Diapers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes, there you go.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "you", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "You're a good diaper changer?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "good", "diaper", "changer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "You're liking being a dad?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "liking", "being", "a", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I'm loving it, man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "loving", "it", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean, you can -- you can give me some advice on fatherhood, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "can", "--", "you", "can", "give", "me", "some", "advice", "on", "fatherhood", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I've got three boys.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "three", "boys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes, because I -- I was neglectful when I saw you at \"America's Got Talent,\" because you were too busy.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "I", "--", "I", "was", "neglectful", "when", "I", "saw", "you", "at", "``", "America", "'s", "Got", "Talent", ",", "''", "because", "you", "were", "too", "busy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "-- than me.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "You're a sports fan, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "sports", "fan", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Because your running joke with me, of course, is it was being -- I'm not famous, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "your", "running", "joke", "with", "me", ",", "of", "course", ",", "is", "it", "was", "being", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "famous", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes, no one knew who you were in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "no", "one", "knew", "who", "you", "were", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Does that sicken you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "sicken", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "You're threatening me with physical violence, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "threatening", "me", "with", "physical", "violence", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Do you wake -- I'm going to ask you this -- do you wake up some mornings and just think, \"Good God, I am lying next to Mariah Carey\"?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wake", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "ask", "you", "this", "--", "do", "you", "wake", "up", "some", "mornings", "and", "just", "think", ",", "``", "Good", "God", ",", "I", "am", "lying", "next", "to", "Mariah", "Carey", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBP", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Every --", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mariah Carey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "-- this is permanent, this is real?", "question_tokens": ["--", "this", "is", "permanent", ",", "this", "is", "real", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mariah Carey"]}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Why were you so sure?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "so", "sure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I was so sure because that was Mariah Carey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "so", "sure", "because", "that", "was", "Mariah", "Carey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Did she know that she was your dream girl?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "know", "that", "she", "was", "your", "dream", "girl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I don't think she did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "But who's the boss at home?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "'s", "the", "boss", "at", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Me, dammit.", "answer_tokens": ["Me", ",", "dammit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 269, "question": "I mean, that's how you get to the top, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "how", "you", "get", "to", "the", "top", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Yes, that's a --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "ORGAN: You're doing it for four hours, right?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "'re", "doing", "it", "for", "four", "hours", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes, four hours.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "four", "hours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "You get up at 1:00 -- you're on air at 1:30?", "question_tokens": ["You", "get", "up", "at", "1:00", "--", "you", "'re", "on", "air", "at", "1:30", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "CD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "One-thirty -- and I'm probably in the studio until about 7:30.", "answer_tokens": ["One-thirty", "--", "and", "I", "'m", "probably", "in", "the", "studio", "until", "about", "7:30", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["1:30?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "When do you sleep?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "sleep", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I don't sleep, man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "sleep", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Do you sleep much at all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sleep", "much", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "No, maybe two hours a night.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "maybe", "two", "hours", "a", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Because it becomes very contagious, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "becomes", "very", "contagious", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any credibility issues with the way that stars are found on these talent shows?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "have", "any", "credibility", "issues", "with", "the", "way", "that", "stars", "are", "found", "on", "these", "talent", "shows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "It's all how it's handle, in my opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "how", "it", "'s", "handle", ",", "in", "my", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "And we do see competitors coming on and trying it on, don't we?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "do", "see", "competitors", "coming", "on", "and", "trying", "it", "on", ",", "do", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "This is like his second hundred million dollar deal, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "like", "his", "second", "hundred", "million", "dollar", "deal", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["Amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "When you see people becoming instantly very famous on this show, how do you feel, as somebody who's in that bubble of fame?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "people", "becoming", "instantly", "very", "famous", "on", "this", "show", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", ",", "as", "somebody", "who", "'s", "in", "that", "bubble", "of", "fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Do you worry about that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I do -- I just hope they know what they're in store for, because I would say if you weigh it out, the things -- the good things about fame are probably smaller than the bad things about fame, especially if you don't know how to handle it, because it's a magnifying glass.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "--", "I", "just", "hope", "they", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "in", "store", "for", ",", "because", "I", "would", "say", "if", "you", "weigh", "it", "out", ",", "the", "things", "--", "the", "good", "things", "about", "fame", "are", "probably", "smaller", "than", "the", "bad", "things", "about", "fame", ",", "especially", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "to", "handle", "it", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "a", "magnifying", "glass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Where do you draw the line, the parity, because you're both very famous?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "draw", "the", "line", ",", "the", "parity", ",", "because", "you", "'re", "both", "very", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Oh, man!", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Is there a line that can still be drawn if you do that, do you think, in terms of personal privacy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "line", "that", "can", "still", "be", "drawn", "if", "you", "do", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "personal", "privacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "There is, but if you give them enough, if you -- if you feed the sharks, they won't attack you.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", ",", "but", "if", "you", "give", "them", "enough", ",", "if", "you", "--", "if", "you", "feed", "the", "sharks", ",", "they", "wo", "n't", "attack", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "When you see other celebrities moaning about being famous, what do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "other", "celebrities", "moaning", "about", "being", "famous", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I hate it, man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hate", "it", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "If you could simplify it for somebody, what's the secret of being a good stand-up?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "simplify", "it", "for", "somebody", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "secret", "of", "being", "a", "good", "stand-up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "There really is none, but if I had to, I would say honesty plus confidence.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "really", "is", "none", ",", "but", "if", "I", "had", "to", ",", "I", "would", "say", "honesty", "plus", "confidence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "How much of your act is topical?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "your", "act", "is", "topical", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "It's -- everything is topical to me, because a lot of it is about my life.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "everything", "is", "topical", "to", "me", ",", "because", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "is", "about", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "-- you got a great honor, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "got", "a", "great", "honor", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Yes, I got to DJ his inauguration party.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "got", "to", "DJ", "his", "inauguration", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "How did that feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Now, it was amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", ",", "it", "was", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "I think he's doing phenomenal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "phenomenal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "ORGAN: -- would you -- would you take him out?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "--", "would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "take", "him", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I don't -- he'd -- he'd have too many bodyguards around him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "he", "'d", "--", "he", "'d", "have", "too", "many", "bodyguards", "around", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":"], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Because you've wanted to, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'ve", "wanted", "to", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "I think there was a time where --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "was", "a", "time", "where", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 663, "question": "What is my talent?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "my", "talent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "If you were entering the show --", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "entering", "the", "show", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "What are you saying singing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "saying", "singing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Your wife is great.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "wife", "is", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 684, "question": "What would you actually do -- other than stand-up comedy, what would you do if you walked on stage on \"AGT\"?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "actually", "do", "--", "other", "than", "stand-up", "comedy", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "if", "you", "walked", "on", "stage", "on", "``", "AGT", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Oh, man, I could --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", ",", "I", "could", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "You want a freestyle?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "a", "freestyle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "How good are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Well, before I got on this show, it was very boring.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "before", "I", "got", "on", "this", "show", ",", "it", "was", "very", "boring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Can you quite believe what's happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "No, it's absolutely phenomenal.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "absolutely", "phenomenal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "And I love that it's an overnight sensation, but it took me 32 years to get there, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "love", "that", "it", "'s", "an", "overnight", "sensation", ",", "but", "it", "took", "me", "32", "years", "to", "get", "there", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "That is amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "What was the act?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "act", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Well, I was always a singer, and I had a band for about 15 years, and I was the lead singer of the band, and I would do impressions of singers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "always", "a", "singer", ",", "and", "I", "had", "a", "band", "for", "about", "15", "years", ",", "and", "I", "was", "the", "lead", "singer", "of", "the", "band", ",", "and", "I", "would", "do", "impressions", "of", "singers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "And that was the magical tipping point, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "was", "the", "magical", "tipping", "point", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Can I sing later?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "sing", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "You can sing later.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "sing", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Do you ever regret losing the anonymity?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "regret", "losing", "the", "anonymity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "No, no, never.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Tell me I'm wrong, Winston was always about the money, right?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "I", "'m", "wrong", ",", "Winston", "was", "always", "about", "the", "money", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Of course, I'm the guy who spends all his money.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "I", "'m", "the", "guy", "who", "spends", "all", "his", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "So, do you want to perform?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "do", "you", "want", "to", "perform", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "Can I do the Roy Orbison?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "do", "the", "Roy", "Orbison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "That's what he wants to hear.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "he", "wants", "to", "hear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roy Orbison"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Are you pleased with it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "pleased", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "I'm very happy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "Is it the culmination of the dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "culmination", "of", "the", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "This is something I've worked my whole life to get to.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "something", "I", "'ve", "worked", "my", "whole", "life", "to", "get", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "And in many ways, saved the kind of life you may have had, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "saved", "the", "kind", "of", "life", "you", "may", "have", "had", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 878, "question": "Was she around to see that?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "around", "to", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "Oh, yes, she's still around and she --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "she", "'s", "still", "around", "and", "she", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "What does she make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "RIMM: She's having probably the best of time, more than anyone.", "answer_tokens": ["RIMM", ":", "She", "'s", "having", "probably", "the", "best", "of", "time", ",", "more", "than", "anyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 908, "question": "Amazing thing to be able to do that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Amazing", "thing", "to", "be", "able", "to", "do", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 909, "answer": "Well, you know, if someone can do it in the family, I'm sure they would.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "someone", "can", "do", "it", "in", "the", "family", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "they", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 917, "question": "It's called \"Michael Grimm,\" right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "called", "``", "Michael", "Grimm", ",", "''", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 918, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Grimm"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 935, "question": "What are you going to sing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "sing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 936, "answer": "I'm going to sing a song off the album.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "sing", "a", "song", "off", "the", "album", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]